nextgenhero.io 2019-03-31

# HERo

Privacy Policy Last updated: 12/7/2018 

DNotes Global is the company responsible for operating NextGen Hero. This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site. 

We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. 

## **Information Collection And Use**

While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you. 

By voluntarily providing us with personal information that may include, but is not limited to your name, occupation, business, and email address when using our website, you irrevocably agree to our use of the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. In instances where private information is given to us, you acknowledge and agree that this information may be stored on our website servers, and servers of authorized third parties.

## **Log Data**

Like many site operators, we reserve the right to collect non-personal information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Site.

This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, browser version, the pages of our Site that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages and other statistics.

In addition, we may use third party services such as Google Analytics that collect, monitor and analyze this information.

This information may be used for purposes such as to improve the content and layout of our website.

## **Communications**

We may use your Personal Information to contact you for purposes not limited to newsletters, surveys, customer service or promotional materials.

## **Cookies**

Cookies are files with small amount of data, which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a web site and stored on your computer’s hard drive. 

Like many sites, we use “cookies” to collect information. You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Site.

## **Security**

The security of your Personal Information is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

## **Third-party websites**

NextGen Hero does not take responsibility or accept any liability for the content and activities by any third party, including cases where NextGen Hero links to external websites. All third party websites have their own privacy policy.

## **Legal disclosure of information**

We reserve the right to preserve or disclose any and all personal information if we are given reason to believe that it is necessary to comply with laws and regulations, or at the request of the government in cases including but not limited to issues of safety, fraud, security, technical issues or to protect our users’ rights or property.

NextGen Hero may share your personal information at the request of law enforcement in cases where legal requirement is proven to do so. 

## **Changes To This Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of 12/7/2018 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page. 

We reserve the right to update or change our Privacy Policy at any time and you should check this Privacy Policy periodically. 

Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. 

If we make any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you either through the email address you have provided us, or by placing a prominent notice on our website. 

## **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please [contact us](https://nextgenhero.io/contact/).
